Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Loreley. Finale des ersten Aktes Uniform Title: Loreley. Selection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 8487, undated; 31142040613203; 65164 (Box 135, Folder 1909)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Plate Number: M.B.9.*, undated; 31142040614169; 65163 (Box 40, Folder 485)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: K.M.455., undated; 31142040614169; 65162 (Box 40, Folder 484)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: M.B.9., undated; 31142040614169; 65161 (Box 40, Folder 482)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.193., undated; 31142040614169; 65160 (Box 40, Folder 483)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: C. 25938, undated; 31142040614169; 65159 (Box 40, Folder 486)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Musikantenprugelei Uniform Title: Musikantenprugelei (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14951 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613302; 65158 (Box 166, Folder 2819)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: O Sons of Art Uniform Title: An die Kunstler, undated; 31142040613567; 65157 (Box 140, Folder 1958)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: On Wings of Song Uniform Title: On Wings of Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Ricordi and Co., Inc. Plate Number: N. Y. 698, undated; 31142040613286; 65156 (Box 168, Folder 2923)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture zu den Hebriden (Fingals Hohle) Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Plate Number: 7848, undated; 31142040614177; 65155 (Box 39, Folder 471)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture zu den Hebriden (Fingals-Hohle) Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.192., undated; 31142040614177; 65154 (Box 39, Folder 472)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture. Die Fingals-Hohle Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer (Jos. Eberle and Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: C. 25225., undated; 31142040614177; 65153 (Box 39, Folder 474)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Rondo Capriccioso Uniform Title: Rondo capriccioso Publisher information: Boston: B. F. Wood Music Company Plate Number: B.F.W. 5290-10, undated; 31142040613518; 65152 (Box 145, Folder 2008)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1838., undated; 31142040614151; 65151 (Box 41, Folder 494)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5150-53, undated; 31142040614151; 65150 (Box 41, Folder 495)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 14174, undated; 31142040614151; 65149 (Box 41, Folder 493)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): Henry Litolff's Verlag Plate Number: 10774, undated; 31142040614151; 65148 (Box 41, Folder 491)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.198., undated; 31142040614151; 65147 (Box 41, Folder 492)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sinfonie fur das grosse Orchester Uniform Title: Symphony no. 1 in c minor, op. 11; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1432, undated; 31142040614383; 65146 (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 7852, undated; 31142040614151; 65145 (Box 41, Folder 487)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: M.B.117.*, undated; 31142040614151; 65144 (Box 41, Folder 490)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: M.B.7., undated; 31142040614151; 65143 (Box 41, Folder 489)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: New York: Associated Music Publisher's Inc. (Breitkopf and Härtel [printer]) Plate Number: Orch.B.281., undated; 31142040614151; 65142 (Box 41, Folder 488)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spinning Song Uniform Title: Songs Without Words. Spinning Song Publisher information: New York: Century Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 433, undated; 31142040613377; 65141 (Box 159, Folder 2570)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spring Song Uniform Title: Gesange, op. 19, no. 1. Frühlingslied Publisher information: New York: Richard A. Saalfield, undated; 31142040612841; 65140 (Box 99, Folder 1262)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spring Song Uniform Title: Songs Without Words. Spring Song Publisher information: New York: Conservatory Publication Society, undated; 31142040612882; 65139 (Box 103, Folder 1379)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphonie No. 1, C minor Uniform Title: Symphony no. 1, op. 11, C minor; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1379 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614383; 65138 (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphonie No. 5, Op. 107 (Reformation Uniform Title: Symphony no. 5 in D Major, op. 107 (Reformation) Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.81/82, undated; 31142040614136; 65137 (Box 43, Folder 507)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphony no. 1, op. 11 Uniform Title: Erste Symphonie, op. 11 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: M.B.1./M.B.1*, undated; 31142040614136; 65136 (Box 43, Folder 505)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphony no. 2, op. 52 Uniform Title: Lobgesang. Sinfonia Plate Number: 6533, undated; 31142040614136; 65135 (Box 43, Folder 504)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Thanks Be to God Uniform Title: Thanks Be to God Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 10188, undated; 31142040613237; 65134 (Box 173, Folder 3152)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Vierte Symphonie Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, op. 90, A Major (Italian symphony) Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: M.B.4/M.B.4.*, undated; 31142040614128; 65133 (Box 44, Folder 512)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Volkslied (Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat) Uniform Title: Volkslied, op. 47, no. 4: Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 8003-3, undated; 31142040613351; 65132 (Box 161, Folder 2636)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Volkslied (Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat) Uniform Title: Volkslied, op. 47, no. 4: Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Theodor Rattig (Jos. Eberle and Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: T.R.197., undated; 31142040613351; 65131 (Box 161, Folder 2637)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: War March of the Priests from Athalia Uniform Title: Athalia. War March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1865-25, undated; 31142040614177; 65130 (Box 39, Folder 467)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: War march of the Priests from Athalia Uniform Title: Athalia. War March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1865-30, undated; 31142040614177; 65129 (Box 39, Folder 468)
  - Composer: Mendolssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Die Erste Walpurgisnacht Uniform Title: Erste Walpurgisnacht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1402, undated; 31142040614144; 65128 (Box 42, Folder 500)
  - Composer: Menzel, J. Title: General Stotzer March Uniform Title: General Stotzer; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 9922-17 1/2, undated; 31142040613088; 65127 (Box 123, Folder 1763)
  - Composer: Menzel, J. Title: Kleine susse Maus Uniform Title: Kleine susse Maus, undated; 31142040613336; 65126 (Box 163, Folder 2738)
  - Composer: Merkler, Andor Title: Gipsy Dance (La Tzigane dansante) Uniform Title: Gipsy Dance; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10603-37, undated; 31142040614136; 65125 (Box 43, Folder 508)
  - Composer: Mertke, Eduard Title: Um Mitternacht Uniform Title: Um Mitternacht Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): P. J. Tonger's Musikverlag (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: P. J. T. 1379 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613237; 65124 (Box 173, Folder 3154)
  - Composer: Methfessel, A. Title: Der deutsche Sangerbund Uniform Title: Deutsche Sangerbund (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 153, undated; 31142040613435; 65123 (Box 153, Folder 2311)
  - Composer: Metra, Olivier Title: La Serenade. Valse Espagnole Uniform Title: La Serenade. Valse Espagnole; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3826-14 1/2, undated; 31142040614136; 65122 (Box 43, Folder 509)
  - Composer: Metz, Aug. C. Title: Sweetheart Serenade Uniform Title: Sweetheart Publisher information: Brooklyn: Aug. C. Metz, undated; 31142040612890; 65121 (Box 104, Folder 1417)
  - Composer: Meyer, Herwegh C. Title: Husarenlied Uniform Title: Husarenlied, undated; 31142040613401; 65120 (Box 156, Folder 2450)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Ballet Music. Divertissement Uniform Title: Ballet Music. Divertissement; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5915-51, undated; 31142040614110; 65119 (Box 45, Folder 523)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Coronation March from The Prophet Uniform Title: Prophete. Marche du sacre; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 15990-42, undated; 31142040614110; 65118 (Box 45, Folder 525)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Der 91ste Psalm Uniform Title: 91. Psalm Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: B.and B. 2426., undated; 31142040613203; 65117 (Box 135, Folder 1901)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Der 91ste Psalm Uniform Title: 91. Psalm Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: B.and B. 2427., undated; 31142040613203; 65116 (Box 135, Folder 1900)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Die Hugenotten. Ouverture Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.200., undated; 31142040614110; 65115 (Box 45, Folder 528)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Die Hugenotten. Ouverture Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.856., undated; 31142040614110; 65114 (Box 45, Folder 527)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: 6319 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614110; 65113 (Box 45, Folder 530)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote and G. Bock Plate Number: 6320 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614110; 65112 (Box 45, Folder 531)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): C. Weinholtz Plate Number: 1099, undated; 31142040614110; 65111 (Box 45, Folder 532)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2082-47, undated; 31142040614110; 65110 (Box 45, Folder 533)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz Uniform Title: Fackeltanz Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): Julius Bauer (Engelmann and Muhlberg [printer]) Plate Number: 840 Engraver: Engelmann and Muhlberg, undated; 31142040612890; 65109 (Box 104, Folder 1426)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Kronungsmarsch aus der Oper Der Prophet Uniform Title: Prophete. Marche du sacre Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 8269, undated; 31142040614110; 65108 (Box 45, Folder 524)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Ouverture et Orgie de l'Opera Les Huguenots Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 5811, undated; 31142040614110; 65107 (Box 45, Folder 529)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Quartetto Le Prophete Uniform Title: Prophete. Selection, undated; 31142040613013; 65106 (Box 116, Folder 1653)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Sommermorgen aus den Hugenotten von Maierbeer Uniform Title: Huguenots. Selection; arr., undated; 31142040613260; 65105 (Box 170, Folder 3001)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Star of the North. Selection Uniform Title: Etoile du nord. Selection; arr. Publisher information: Boston: Jean White Plate Number: 1430-47-5, undated; 31142040614110; 65104 (Box 45, Folder 526)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, E. Title: Serenade Roccoco Uniform Title: Serenade Roccoco Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth and Co. Plate Number: B. and Co. 273, undated; 31142040612817; 65103 (Box 96, Folder 1193)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, Erik Title: Dann ist's die rechte Zeit Uniform Title: Dann ist's die rechte Zeit Plate Number: 7102, undated; 31142040613435; 65102 (Box 153, Folder 2318)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, Erik Title: Venetianisches Gondellied Uniform Title: Venetianisches Gondellied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6406 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613443; 65101 (Box 152, Folder 2282)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Clare Dettin. Vorspiel zum dritten Aufzuge Uniform Title: Clare Dettin. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel Plate Number: 11548 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614086; 65100 (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Clare Dettin. Vorspiel zum dritten Aufzuge Uniform Title: Clare Dettin. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel Plate Number: 11682, undated; 31142040614086; 65099 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Das Fest Uniform Title: Fest Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12952 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612866; 65098 (Box 101, Folder 1324)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Der Blumen Rache Uniform Title: Blumen Rache Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12217 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613153; 65097 (Box 130, Folder 1872)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Der Blumen Rache Uniform Title: Blumen Rache Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12219 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613153; 65096 (Box 130, Folder 1873)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Die Mondfee Uniform Title: Mondfee Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 17618, undated; 31142040613229; 65095 (Box 174, Folder 3204)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Gebt mir vom Becher nur den Schaum Uniform Title: Op. 100, no. 2. Gebt mir vom Becher nur den Schaum Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22928, undated; 31142040613344; 65094 (Box 162, Folder 2676)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Gothen-Treue Uniform Title: Gothen-Treue Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G. H. 1787, undated; 31142040613393; 65093 (Box 157, Folder 2505)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Konigin Waldlieb Uniform Title: Konigin Waldlieb Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9307 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612734; 65092 (Box 88, Folder 1106)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Konigin Waldlieb Uniform Title: Konigin Waldlieb Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9308 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613336; 65091 (Box 163, Folder 2748)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Tanzreigen Uniform Title: Tanzreigen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 2351 Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612734; 65090 (Box 88, Folder 1107)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Tanzreigen Uniform Title: Tanzreigen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.2353. Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612866; 65089 (Box 101, Folder 1319)
  - Composer: Mezzacapo, E. Title: Sympathie. Valse Uniform Title: Sympathie Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Hawkes and Son Plate Number: H and S. 3591, undated; 31142040613070; 65088 (Box 122, Folder 1757)
  - Composer: Michaelis, Theodor Title: Die Schmiede im Walde Uniform Title: Schmiede im Walde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ruhle and Wendling Plate Number: 218, undated; 31142040614128; 65087 (Box 44, Folder 514)
  - Composer: Michaelis, Theodor Title: Die Schmiede im Walde Uniform Title: Schmiede im Walde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ruhle and Wendling Plate Number: R. and W. 217, undated; 31142040614128; 65086 (Box 44, Folder 515)
  - Composer: Minnigerode, Meade, George S. Pomeroy, and Tod B. Galloway Title: The Whiffenpoof Song Uniform Title: Whiffenpoof Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: Miller Music Corporation Plate Number: 579-6, undated; 31142040613427; 65085 (Box 154, Folder 2356)
  - Composer: Miro, Enrique Title: Mercedes. Valse Espagnole Uniform Title: Mercedes. Valse Espagnole; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22532, undated; 31142040614128; 65084 (Box 44, Folder 516)
  - Composer: Moellendorff, Willy von Title: Regenhusch im Fruhjahr Uniform Title: Regenhusch im Fruhjahr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 3289, undated; 31142040613260; 65083 (Box 170, Folder 2997)
  - Composer: Mohr, Andreas Title: Festmarsch Uniform Title: Festmarsch, undated; 31142040613138; 65082 (Box 128, Folder 1867)
  - Composer: Mohr, Herman Title: Columbus Uniform Title: Colon Publisher information: Philadelphia: Herman Mohr, undated; 31142040613450; 65081 (Box 151, Folder 2213)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter, undated; 31142040613054; 65080 (Box 120, Folder 1716)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 201 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613419; 65079 (Box 155, Folder 2429)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 202 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613419; 65078 (Box 155, Folder 2430)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 226 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613419; 65077 (Box 155, Folder 2431)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Hoffnung Uniform Title: Hoffnung Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613344; 65076 (Box 162, Folder 2663)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Hymnus Uniform Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus (Marsh and Co., Philadelphia [printer]), undated; 31142040612858; 65075 (Box 100, Folder 1299)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus Uniform Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 150 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612858; 65074 (Box 100, Folder 1298)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: O lieb' so lang du lieben kannst Uniform Title: O lieb' so lang du lieben kannst Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): M. Bahn Verlag (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: M. 3697 B. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613286; 65073 (Box 168, Folder 2905)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Auf Offner See Uniform Title: Auf offner See, undated; 31142040612817; 65072 (Box 96, Folder 1202)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Das Dichtergrab am Rhein Uniform Title: Dichtergrab am Rhein Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613419; 65071 (Box 155, Folder 2395)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Der Rheingauer Wein Uniform Title: Rheingauer Wein Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 22369.1, undated; 31142040613278; 65070 (Box 169, Folder 2977)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Die Gestirne Uniform Title: Gestirne Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 23081., undated; 31142040613229; 65069 (Box 174, Folder 3202)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Hymne an die Nacht Uniform Title: Hymne an die Nacht Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre (Kohler and Teller, Offenbach a/M [printer]) Plate Number: 10279, undated; 31142040613583; 65068 (Box 138, Folder 1928)